safehaven.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy

Leacap Ltd T/as http://safehaven.com the "Data controller" takes your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when the Data Controller collects personal information about you and how the Data Controller will use your personal data.

This policy applies to information we collect about:

  * visitors to our website;
  * people who do business with us/register for our service.

### 1\. The information we collect about you

When you do business with us/register for our service we may collect the following personal information from you:

  * name;
  * postal address, email address, telephone number.
  * Credit/debit card details

### 2\. How we will use the information about you

We gather this information to allow us to process your registration, and to help provide our content and services. The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your subscription and the provision of our website and subscription service.

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us to develop our website and our services. We may also provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you.

From time to time we may provide your information to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the goods or services we provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you by post, email or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our services.

### 3\. Marketing

We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our website or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send a blank email message to [admin@safehaven.com](mailto:admin@safehaven.com). If you agree to us providing you with marketing information, you can always opt out at a later date.

We may also want to provide you with related information from third parties we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an email to [admin@safehaven.com](mailto:admin@safehaven.com). If you agree to us providing you with third party marketing information, you can always opt out at a later date.

We may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish us to disclose your information in this way, please send an email to [admin@safehaven.com](mailto:admin@safehaven.com).

### 4\. Our use of cookies and other information-gathering technologies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information. The information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. For further information about cookies visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases some of our website features may not function if you remove cookies from your browser.

### Our use of cookies

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, your computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally.

We will not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by our website, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The 'Help' function within your browser should tell you how.

Alternatively, you may wish to visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. You will also find details on how to delete cookies from your machine as well as more general information about cookies.

Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of our website. If you wish to view your cookie code, just click on a cookie to open it. You’ll see a short string of text and numbers. The numbers are your identification card, which can only be seen by the server that gave you the cookie. For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone you will need to refer to your handset manual.

To opt-out of third-parties collecting any data regarding your interaction on our website, please refer to their websites for further information.

### 5\. How we protect your information

We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use of the Internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet.

### 6\. Overseas transfers

The information you provide may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area ('EEA') that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and restrictions on its use as set out in this policy. However, we will take steps to ensure adequate protections are in place to ensure the security of your information. The EEA comprises the EU member states plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers for the purposes specified above.

### 7\. Access to your information and updating and correcting your information

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please send an email to [admin@safehaven.com](mailto:admin@safehaven.com). We may make a small charge for this service.

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to the Data Controller changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details, or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an email to admin@safehaven.com.You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.

### 8\. Sale of business

If the Data Controller's business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

### 9\. Your consent

By submitting your personal information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy.

### 10\. Changes to privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. This privacy policy was last updated on 10th July 2012.

### 11\. How to contact the Data Controller

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an email to [admin@safehaven.com](mailto:admin@safehaven.com).

### 12\. Links to other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

### 13\. Payment

We currently use the PayPal checkout system for all payments. For details of how PayPal protects your financial information please visit <https://www.paypal.com/>.
